const questions = {
    english: [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: "What is the synonym of 'happy'?",
            options: ["Sad", "Joyful", "Angry", "Lonely"],
            answer: "Joyful",
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            question: "Which is a noun?",
            options: ["Run", "Quickly", "Apple", "Bright"],
            answer: "Apple",
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            question: "What is the antonym of 'dark'?",
            options: ["Night", "Day", "Light", "Shady"],
            answer: "Light",
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question: "What is the synonym of 'dark'?",
            options: ["Night", "Day", "Light", "Shady"],
            answer: "Shady",
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            question: "What is the synonym of 'happy'?",
            options: ["Sad", "Joyful", "Angry", "Lonely"],
            answer: "Joyful",
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            question: "Which is a noun?",
            options: ["Run", "Quickly", "Apple", "Bright"],
            answer: "Apple",
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            question: "What is the antonym of 'dark'?",
            options: ["Night", "Day", "Light", "Shady"],
            answer: "Light",
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            question: "What is the synonym of 'dark'?",
            options: ["Night", "Day", "Light", "Shady"],
            answer: "Shady",
        },
    ],
    marathi: [
        {
            id: 9,
            question: "Translate 'apple' in Hindi",
            options: ["सेब", "गाजर", "किताब", "खिड़की"],
            answer: "सेब",
        },
        {
            id: 10,
            question: "Translate 'book' in Hindi",
            options: ["बाहर", "खाना", "किताब", "खिड़की"],
            answer: "किताब",
        },
        {
            id: 11,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'माता'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Mother",
        },
        {
            id: 12,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'pita'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Father",
        },
        {
            id: 13,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'माता'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Mother",
        },
        {
            id: 14,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'pita'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Father",
        },
        {
            id: 15,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'माता'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Mother",
        },
        {
            id: 16,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'pita'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Father",
        },
        {
            id: 17,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'माता'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Mother",
        },
        {
            id: 18,
            question: "What is the meaning of 'pita'?",
            options: ["Father", "Mother", "Brother", "Sister"],
            answer: "Father",
        },
    ],
    generalknowledge: [
        {
            id: 19,
            question: "2 + 2 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 20,
            question: "5 * 3 = ?",
            options: ["15", "10", "8", "12"],
            answer: "15",
        },
        {
            id: 21,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 22,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 23,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 24,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 25,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 26,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 27,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 28,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 29,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
    ],
    mathsReasoning: [
        {
            id: 19,
            question: "2 + 2 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 20,
            question: "5 * 3 = ?",
            options: ["15", "10", "8", "12"],
            answer: "15",
        },
        {
            id: 21,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 22,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 23,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 24,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 25,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 26,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 27,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 28,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 29,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
    ],
    mathsAlgebra: [
        {
            id: 19,
            question: "2 + 2 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 20,
            question: "5 * 3 = ?",
            options: ["15", "10", "8", "12"],
            answer: "15",
        },
        {
            id: 21,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 22,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 23,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 24,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 25,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 26,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 27,
            question: "12 / 4 = ?",
            options: ["3", "4", "2", "6"],
            answer: "3",
        },
        {
            id: 28,
            question: "7 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "4",
        },
        {
            id: 29,
            question: "3 - 3 = ?",
            options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            answer: "3",
        },
    ],
};

export default questions;
